

Anna Kuliga

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+47 925 35 197 +48 785 036 017

a.kuliga2@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/annakuliga/

PROFILE

Innovative, creative and professional. Graduate from Linguistics. SheCodes Alumni, working with React.js.

I am a cheerful, ambitious and resilient person. I love my job and achieving milestones working with a team. In my professional life I follow perfection.

Not afraid of challenges and like to learn new things to get more experience.

LANGUAGES

Polish - Native English - C1/C2 French - Intermediate Norwegian - Basic

NATIONALITY: POLISH

Currently based : Oslo, Norway

EDUCATION

SheCodes October 2022 - March 2023

Frontend Development

University of Maria Curie- Skłodowska in Lublin

MA : Applied Linguistics October 2018 - July 2020

BA: Applied Linguistics October 2015- July 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

YOUNIVERSE Language Academy | 2021-2023

I have been running successfully the company as the owner. Gained knowledge in the field of business and administration of a small company. My duties include contact, maintenance the good relations with current and future clients.

YOUNIVERSE Language Academy | 2021- 2023

I have been teaching students at all levels and preparing them for various language examinations and certifications. Working remotely and on site in Poland, remotely from Norway. Offering homeschooling and private English classes.

YOUNIVERSE Language Academy | 2021- 2023

Translating non-specialised texts and documents from Polish into English and English into Polish.

Internship at Terapia i Poradnictwo Psychologiczne Patrycja Grabias | Rzeszów 2019-2020

Internship at Translation Agency `ling4u` | Krosno 2017-2019

Anna Kuliga

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

TOOLS

Bootstrap, Figma, Git, NPM, VS Code

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js

USEFUL LINKS



https://github.com/AnnaKuliga



https://fanciful-pascaf84a3e.netlify.app



https://www.shecodes.io/grad uates/57519-anna-kuliga



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ in annakuliga/

SKILLS

Administration and office management **API**

Bootstrap

Communication skills

Contact with potential clients

CSS

E - learning

Editor

Excellent interpersonal skills

Figma

Front-end Development

Git / GitLab/ GitHub

Hosting

HTML

JavaScript

Microsoft Office

Microsoft Word

NPM

React.is

Responsive Web Development

SE₀

Teaching

Team work management

Time management

Translations

Writing skills

CERTIFICATIONS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Valid Certificate ID:

bcfee2244b75c4d6eec9976d809dc39b

SheCodes React | March 2023

Valid Certificate ID: 85f5cd4538328fac473fa1a24557fbf5

Valid Certificate ID:

ebccd0f3f2c3d492aa75a68a28c03688

SheCodes Responsive | January 2023

Valid Certificate ID: bde31d85b1d12c975cec9d5fae6649ab Valid Certificate ID: 61dd67fcc0db7d907622734d1ab871e4

SheCodes Plus | December 2022

Valid Certificate ID: a0e68c9871cad347b539af1b14d9ab5b Valid Certificate ID: a161d71cb6865b0e9db7b2c995120d7a

SheCodes Basics | October 2022

Valid Certificate ID: 798fdd5ee43471bcc4a69ddb46fe60ab Valid Certificate ID: 44a5d15a75b55a37bf1f07dcad4f3220

Hobbies

Photography, Travels, Sports, Pets, Languages